http://www.freebeautytips.org/privacy.html

Privacy Statement
General.
Our company and our software publisher respect the privacy of every individual who visits our website. This Privacy Statement outlines the information we will collect and how we will use that information. This Statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected when you visit our website.
Personal Information.
We will not collect your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address unless you provide it to us voluntarily. However, we may attempt to collect such information if we believe your use of this website violates any laws. If you do not want this information collected, please do not submit it to us.
If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the e-mail address listed at the bottom of this Statement. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files.
When you do provide us with personal information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our services. We may also use that information to contact you. However, we will not provide that information to third parties.
Children.
We have no intention of collecting any personal information (that is, name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from individuals under eighteen years of age. Where appropriate, we will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our website. If a child has provided us with personally-identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the e-mail address listed at the bottom of this Statement to request that this information be deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our existing files.
Other information collected automatically.
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the URL of the website from which you linked or clicked to our website.
Information we may place automatically on your computer's hard drive.
When you view our website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor our website to better match your interests and preferences.
Some of our advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing California restuarant ads to someone in California, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing scrapbooking ads to someone who frequents scrapbooking sites). With most Internet Browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Specific to the Google Ads displayed on this site Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads our your site. Their DART cookie enables them and their partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Web surfers may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy
Who to contact.
If you have submitted personal information through this website and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at the following e-mail address: info@freebeautytips.org. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files.
Sponser
Get Weekly Beauty Tips
Receive FREE weekly beauty tips to your email box! Get a free Beauty eBook as our gift to you.
Name:
Email:
**We respect privacy! Your email address is never shared.
Contact Us |
Privacy |
Legal | Affiliate Disclosure | About Us
Copyright (c) 2003-2012 Free Beauty Tips. All rights reserved.
